<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MysteriousMe</string>
    <string name="name">Flavia Augusta</string>
    <string name="bio">"Flavia Augusta: A Spirited Adventurer Unleashing Creativity
Flavia Augusta is a dynamic soul with an insatiable thirst for adventure and a deep passion for creativity. Born with an innate curiosity, Flavia has always sought out novel experiences and embraced challenges as opportunities for growth.

With an artistic spirit at the core, Flavia has dabbled in various forms of creative expression. From brush strokes on canvas to dance moves on stage, Flavia's creativity knows no bounds. With each artistic endeavor, she weaves a captivating narrative, bringing emotions to life and captivating audiences with her vibrant imagination.

Beyond the realm of artistry, Flavia's adventurous spirit has taken her to the far corners of the world. From trekking through ancient rainforests to exploring hidden gems in bustling cities, she immerses herself in diverse cultures, gaining a profound appreciation for the richness and beauty of our planet.

Fueling Flavia's explorations is an unwavering belief in the power of knowledge. With a thirst for learning, she delves into various subjects, constantly expanding her intellectual horizons. Whether it's exploring scientific breakthroughs or unraveling the depths of human psychology, Flavia seeks to understand the intricate tapestry of life and share her discoveries with others.

In addition to her passion for creativity and knowledge, Flavia is a compassionate advocate for the environment and social justice. She actively engages in initiatives aimed at protecting our planet, promoting sustainable practices, and fostering equality for all. With her strong voice and unwavering dedication, she strives to create a positive impact and inspire change.

Flavia Augusta's magnetic energy and zest for life are contagious, drawing people into her orbit of inspiration and excitement. Whether through her artistic creations, her global explorations, or her commitment to making a difference, Flavia continues to leave an indelible mark on the world, reminding us all to embrace our passions and embrace the unknown, and live life to the fullest.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="yellow_star">yellow star\n</string>
    <string name="what_is_your_nickname">What is your nickname ?</string>
</resources>